        
           ~*~{ TINT TIMER INSTRUCTIONS }~*~
     
      This Chrome Extension is designed to be a 
      productivity assistant that helps you focus
      by tinting the screen of the chrome browser.

   We were inspired by the Pomodoro Study Method, which
   breaks study sessions into 25 minute intervals with 
   short breaks inbetween. This extension allows 
   sessions of time to be associated with a color tint on 
   the screen. This allows the user to pyschologically 
   associate certain colors with certain tasks, and plan
   out their day more effectively.This color tint will 
   serve as an active reminder to focus on the current task.


   Features:

   Create different sessions, each with individual
   colors and names. Once started, your sessions will
   activate, tinting your screen and beginning the
   countdown until your sessions end. Pausing will
   remove the tint and stop the timer until you resume
   your session. At the top there is an ETA that will 
   tell you when all your sessions will finish.

-------------------------------------------------------------
 *Open the extension by clicking the Color Wheel image in
       the top right corner of your chrome window*


   HOW TO USE:
	1. Enter Session Name
	2. Enter Session Time
	3. Choose Session Color
	4. Add Session to Session List
	5. Repeat Steps 1-4 as many times as you want
	6. Hit Start Button :-)

-------------------------------------------------------------
  TIPS AND TRICKS:
                            
			     Click Here to Toggle Theme!     
   _________________________________________________↓___
  |______________________________________________Theme|*| 
  |      SESSIONS      |                                |
  | ------------------ |  While sessions are running    |
  |                    |  press CTRL-SPACE for an       |
  |  You can drag      |  on-screen update!             |
  |  and drop sessions |                                |
  |  to change their   |  Custom colors will be saved   |
  |  order!!           |  and stored, even with the     |
  |                    |  extension closed!             |  
   _____________________________________________________

-------------------------------------------------------------
Created by NWAPW Team Eric, Bruce, Nate and Fiona         =)
